Guide to the Cable 13 Videotapes, 1976-2009 UA.09.13.0008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2016-0027, 1976-2009; 2
  - Special Events #4, 1989 November 05 (Box 53, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0531)
    Program Length: 23mins; Cable13 tape number: 8908-60-702; Other notes: Congressman Bill Gray Rev. Will Keim
  - Under the Bridge, 1989 November 12 (Box 49, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0532)
    Program Length: 31mins40secs; Cable13 tape number: 8908-60-704; Other notes: Show #3
  - Sportsline # 6, 1989 November 12 (Box 51, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0533)
    Program Length: 31mins40secs; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-660; Other notes: PHI DELT vs DELTA SIG
  - Bull Session #6, 1989 November 16 (Box 47, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0534)
    Program Length: 30mins1sec; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-675; Other notes: Berlin Wall, Guests: Dr. Claudia Koonz, Pat Tagney, Kirsten Thayer
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1989 November 16 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0535)
    Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-695
  - Cameron Corner #1, 1989 November 20 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0536)
    Program Length: 60mins; Other notes: Season Premiere With Coach K
  - Bull Session #7, 1989 November 30 (Box 47, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0537)
    Program Length: 26mins10secs; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-676; Other notes: Jabberwocky: Craig McKinney, Walter Keay, Donald "Bird" Wright - DUFS, Dimitri Korhais
  - Nightly News, 198? October 27 (Box 23, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0116)
    Program Length: 12mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: ST 59
  - Under the Bridge - Best of, 1990 (Box 51, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0049)
    Program Length: 60mins02secs; Other notes: Compilation of 1989-90 season
  - Kaspar #1, 1990 (Box 104, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0050)
    Program Length: 59mins57secs; Cable13 tape number: 1 of 2; Other notes: Tape # 8807-60-272
  - Kaspar #2, 1990 (Box 53, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0051)
    Program Length: 30mins54secs; Cable13 tape number: 2 of 2
  - Under the Bridge #3, 1990 Fall (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0585)
    Program Length: 31mins47secs; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-679
  - Hoof 'n Horn "Moby Dick", 1990 November (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0625)
    Program Length: 45mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2)
  - Hoof 'n Horn "Moby Dick", 1990 November (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0626)
    Program Length: 33mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: 8908-60-718
  - Inside Duke Year 3 Show 1, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0629)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-3--057; Other notes: Recycling, student film Matt Hammer
  - Inside Duke Show 2, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0630)
    Program Length: 13mins26secs; Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-040; Other notes: Special Edition Persian Gulf
  - Durham 27706 #1, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0631)
    Program Length: 39mins41secs; Other notes: MASTER TAPE
  - Durham 27706 Anniversary Special, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0632)
    Program Length: 61mins16secs
  - Under the Bridge, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0633)
    Program Length: 12mins; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-685; Other notes: Pilot
  - Under the Bridge, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0634)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-038; Other notes: Combined "UTB & "Happy Head"
  - Under the Bridge, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0635)
    Program Length: 29mins07secs; Other notes: 2nd Pilot 'Date From Hell' 'Ant Watching'
  - Under the Bridge #4, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0636)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-042
  - Under the Bridge #5, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0637)
    Program Length: 16mins08secs; Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-052
  - Under the Bridge #6, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0638)
    Program Length: 18mins06secs; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-673
  - Under the Bridge #7, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0639)
    Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-681
  - Best of Under the Bridge, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0640)
    Program Length: 57mins48secs; Other notes: For Beth at Student TV UNC
  - Duke Film & Video Program Student Films, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0641)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape #1; Other notes: 1.Honor thy Father - Jelena McAfee 2.1000 Words-J. Whetstone 3.Untitled-Clark Mathis 4.Little Red Riding Hood-Ian Wickershaim 5.The Beast Called Ma -A. Kelly 6.The Final Lecture-Bill Weydig
  - Duke Film & Video Program Student Films, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0642)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape #2; Other notes: 1.I Am on Top of Me-Liz Asch (12mins) 2.Queen of Spades-Justin Mitchell (6mins) 3.Recently-Joy Chen (17mins) 4.Animation-Annissa Metzger (3mins)
  - Duke Film & Video Program Student Films, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0643)
    Program Length: 55mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape #3; Other notes: 1.Taken In-Max Day 2.Chain Letter-Tim Haddock 3.All About Eve-Laura Tawney 4.From Blood to Wine-David Messinger 5.Trephining-Michael McIntyre 6.New Hope Creek-Triangle Conservancy Project
  - Duke Film & Video Program Student Films, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0644)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape #4; Other notes: 1.Ecce homo-J. Hexner (22mins) 2.Hunter's Prey-John Reidy(13mins) 3.Untitled-Bob Smithwick (7mins) 4.Superdude!-S. Reissner
  - Cameron Corner, 1990-1991 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0645)
    Program Length: 24mins57secs
  - Inside Duke - Opening, 1990-1991 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0646)
    Other notes: Opening Montage w/ Theme music, revised
  - Duke Yearlook, 1990 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0008)
  - Duke Union Student Video Contest, 1990 April (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0047)
    Cable13 tape number: copy 4
  - Duke Union Student Video Contest, 1990 April (Box 96, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0048)
    Cable13 tape number: copy 2
  - Duke Union Student Video Contest, 1990 April (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0039)
    Cable13 tape number: copy 1
  - Final Film Project, 1990 December (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0049)
    Other notes: by Rachel Bertin
  - Cameron Corner #2, 1990 January 21 (Box 105, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0611)
    Program Length: 29mins43secs; Cable13 tape number: #2; Other notes: Brian Davis, Ron Morris, Dan Bernstein, Mark Mayer
  - Sportsline #7, 1990 January 22 (Box 51, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0612)
    Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-682; Other notes: Stonehenge V. Army
  - Sportsline #8, 1990 January 24 (Box 51, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0613)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-689; Other notes: BOG v. KAPPA SIG
  - Sportsline #9, 1990 January 24 (Box 51, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0614)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-697; Other notes: PHI PSI v. SIGMA CHI
  - Sportsline #10, 1990 January 29 (Box 51, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0615)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-655; Other notes: PHI DELT v. SIGMA NU
  - Bull Session #8, 1990 February 01 (Box 47, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0586)
    Program Length: 30mins15secs; Other notes: Levinsohn, Keay, Manett, Topics: Young Trustee, Bush's state of the union, Eastern Europe
  - Trinity Food #1: Baggers vs Boggers, 1990 February 01 (Box 66, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0587)
    Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-677
  - Inside Duke - Duke in the '90s, 1990 February 03 (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0588)
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1990 February 04 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0589)
    Program Length: 30mins4secs; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-671; Other notes: Speakers: Tom Finke, J. P. Ziegler
  - Under the Bridge, 1990 February 04 (Box 49, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0590)
    Program Length: 25mins42secs; Cable13 tape number: 8908-60-725; Other notes: Show #4
  - Duke Sportscenter #5, 1990 February 04 (Box 50, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0591)
    Program Length: 15mins30secs; Other notes: Duke-ND Duke-Clemson Thomas Hill Fencing
  - Cameron Corner #3, 1990 February 05 (Box 49, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0592)
    Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-657; Other notes: Thomas Hill, Mike Bernardino, Rodney Peele, Dan Bernstein, Steve Goldberg
  - Inside Duke #4, 1990 February 10 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0593)
    Program Length: 32mins; Cable13 tape number: Year 2; Other notes: Prod: M. Hitti, Duke in the 1990s, Panel Discussion: Paul Levinsohn, Maureen Cullins, Ted Wang, Harold Wingood, Connie Pearcy, Eric Dozier
  - Inside Duke #4, 1990 February 11 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0594)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Year 2; Other notes: Prod: Miranda Hitti, Duke in the 1990s, Cable Vision Dub
  - Duke Sportscenter #6, 1990 February 11 (Box 51, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0595)
    Program Length: 15mins30secs; Other notes: Vitale Promo Hoops Highlights90 Brickey Jam Session
  - Cameron Corner #4, 1990 February 12 (Box 49, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0596)
    Program Length: 30mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-656; Other notes: Quin Snyde, Jim Farley, Mark Jaffe, Dan Bernstein, Steve Goldberg
  - One-On-One #5, 1990 February 12 (Box 50, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0597)
    Program Length: 32mins; Other notes: Dick Vitale Mark Mayer
  - Bull Session #9, 1990 February 15 (Box 47, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0598)
    Program Length: 29mins20secs; Other notes: Dr. Sheridan Johns, Walter Keay, Rob Lavitt, Topics: The State of South of Africa
  - Bull Session #9, 1990 February 15 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0599)
    Program Length: 29mins15secs; Other notes: (for Durham Cablevision) Rob Lavitt, Walter Keay, Dr. Sheridan Johns, Topics: South African Politics/The Release of Mandela, Prod: George Plamondon
  - Under the Bridge, 1990 February 18 (Box 49, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0600)
    Program Length: 30mins26secs
  - One-On-One #6, 1990 February 18 (Box 50, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0601)
    Program Length: 28mins; Other notes: John Feinstein Paul Levinsohn Mark Mayer
  - Duke Sportscenter #7, 1990 February 18 (Box 51, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0602)
    Program Length: 17mins; Other notes: Wake Forest E. Carolina ACC Top 25 Boxing
  - Cameron Corner #5, 1990 February 19 (Box 49, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0603)
    Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-652; Other notes: Alan Abdelnaby,CharlesChandler,DwayneBallum,RodneyPeele,SteveGoldberg
  - Sportsline #11, 1990 February 19 (Box 52, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0604)
    Program Length: 25mins; Other notes: BOG v, SIGMA NU
  - Inside Duke, 1990 February 25 (Box 42, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0605)
    Program Length: 22mins; Cable13 tape number: Year 2; Other notes: Show #5 Teach for America, Visiting Soviet students, Primate center Exec Prod: Miranda Hitti
  - Inside Duke #5, 1990 February 25 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0606)
    Program Length: 22mins; Cable13 tape number: Year 2; Other notes: Teach for America, Visiting Soviet Students, Primate Center For U-NET
  - Special Events: "Safe Sex", 1990 February 25 (Box 52, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0607)
    Program Length: 29mins18secs; Cable13 tape number: 1 of 1; Other notes: Safe sex panel discussion
  - Inside Duke Year 2 Show 5, 1990 February 25 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0608)
    Program Length: 22mins; Cable13 tape number: Cablevision Dub; Other notes: Teach for America, Visiting Soviet Students, Primate Center For U-NET
  - Cameron Corner #6, 1990 February 26 (Box 50, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0609)
    Program Length: 35mins; Cable13 tape number: #6; Other notes: Brian Davis, Al Featherstan, Andy Layton, Dan Bernstein, Dave Glenn
  - Sportsline #12, 1990 February 27 (Box 52, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0610)
    Program Length: 26mins42secs; Other notes: Stonehenge v. PHI PSI
  - The Know Show, 1990 March 01 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0616)
    Program Length: 30mins10secs; Cable13 tape number: #1; Other notes: Black History Month Game Show, Crew: Sam Moon, Roger, Plamandon, Manchuck
  - Cameron Corner #7, 1990 March 05 (Box 50, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0617)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: #7; Other notes: Pete Gaudet, Bob Harris, Mark McLaughlin, Dan Bernstein
  - Thelonious Monk Institute concert 1990, 1990 March 24 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0618)
    Cable13 tape number: 1 of 2; Other notes: Miranda Hitti producer
  - Thelonious Monk Institute concert 1990, 1990 March 24 (Box 54, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0619)
    Cable13 tape number: 2 of 2; Other notes: Miranda Hitti producer
  - Sportscenter #8, 1990 March 25 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0620)
    Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-664; Other notes: Final Four Preview, Mike Koldan int. Baseball preview, Prod: Steve Goldberg
  - Date/Acquaintance Rape at Duke, 1990 March 29 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0621)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Panel Discussion: Dr. David Lisak, Dr. Susan Roth, Dr. Wendy Luttnell, Crew: Miranda Hitti, Deidre Glasser
  - Date/Acquaintance Rape at Duke, 1990 March 29 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0622)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Panel Discussion: Dr. David Lisak, Dr. Susan Roth, Dr. Wendy Luttnell, Crew: Miranda Hitti, Deidre Glasser
  - Special Events: Spike Lee, 1990 March 30 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0623)
    Program Length: 62mins7secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: clips of press conference and speech, crew: Katie Green, Kerry Ripp, George Plamondon
  - Special Events: Spike Lee, 1990 March 30 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0624)
    Program Length: 24mins40secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: question/answer period
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1990 April 01 (Box 105, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0576)
    Program Length: 29mins; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-653; Other notes: Speakers: Roger Enrico (PepsiCo), Dick Schultz (NCAA), Randy Stoddard, Tom Finke, Prod: Beverley Sobel
  - Rocky Mountain Fever, 1990 April 02 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0577)
    Program Length: 12mins
  - Inside Duke #6, 1990 April 08 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0578)
    Program Length: 27mins40secs; Cable13 tape number: Year 2; Other notes: Special Report - Date/Acquaintance Rape at Duke
  - Inside Duke #6, 1990 April 08 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0579)
    Program Length: 27mins40secs; Cable13 tape number: U-Net Copy; Other notes: Special Report - Date/Acquaintance Rape at Duke
  - Inside Duke #6, 1990 April 08 (Box 48, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0580)
    Program Length: 27mins40secs; Cable13 tape number: Cablevision Copy; Other notes: Special Report - Date/Acquaintance Rape at Duke
  - Sportsline #13, 1990 April 09 (Box 52, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0581)
    Program Length: 30mins40secs; Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-678; Other notes: BOG v. Stonehenge
  - Under the Bridge, 1990 April 09 (Box 53, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0582)
    Program Length: 32mins10secs; Cable13 tape number: #6; Other notes: Various Humor
  - Sportscenter #9, 1990 April 15 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0583)
    Program Length: 20mins; Other notes: Rocky Mountain Fever, Robert Brickey Highlights
  - One-On-One #7, 1990 April 23 (Box 50, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0584)
    Program Length: 32mins; Cable13 tape number: 8812-30-645; Other notes: Lute Olson Mark Mayer
  - R. Crumb Comix - Duke Drama, 1990 Fall (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0953)
    Program Length: 58mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2)
  - Inside Duke - Student film, 1990 October 30 (Box 96, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0628)
    Cable13 tape number: #1; Other notes: B-roll
  - Cameron Corner #1, 1990 November 27 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0627)
    Program Length: 56mins45secs; Other notes: Tommy Amaker
  - Gothic Fall, 1991 (Box 45, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0052)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-60-027; Other notes: D. Michael G. Mitchell, Dub - 3rd Generation
  - Cameron Corner Promo, 1991 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0053)
    Other notes: w/ Dick Vitale, Brent Musberger, Maru Albert, Jimmy V, Coach K, Mike Patrick, and Al Maguire
  - Grant Hill in C-13 studio-Fuqua vision Promo, 1991 (Box 96, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0054)
    Other notes: Raw footage
  - FBI Recruitment, 1991 August (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0649)
  - Talk to Me #1, 1991 Fall (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0651)
    Program Length: 32mins; Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-009
  - Talk to Me #2, 1991 Fall (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0652)
    Other notes: Guest: Tony Tjan
  - Film & Video Student Compilation Reel, 1991 Fall (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0653)
    Program Length: 53mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: 1.Van Gogh A Go Go-Chris Davis(7:10) 2.Getting There-Jerry Surrat (9:45) 3.The Bookworm Turns-Hugh Fitzpatrick(11:50) 4.untitled-Lee Fielder(6:45) 5.untitled-Mark Wasmer(10) 6.The New Messiah-Adam Pasztory(6:45), for F&V Theory and Practice-Fred Burns
  - Film & Video Student Compilation Reel, 1991 Fall (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0654)
    Program Length: 52mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: 1.Duke Recycles: The Movie-Chad Hood(10) 2.Object of Power-Lisa Klink(6:45) 3.Sexual Harassment, The Thomas Hearings, and How We Handle Information-Megan McShea(9:45) 4.Dearly Beloved-Terry Satterfield(8) 5.Bastions of Solitude-Eduardo Morell(5:50) 6.untitled-Nancy Delgado(10:10)
  - Black History Month Game Show, 1991 February (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0655)
    Program Length: 29mins; Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-053; Other notes: Prod: Chris Manchuck, George Plamondon
  - "Perceptions of Tranquility", 1991 March (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0670)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Master; Other notes: M. Goldstein, T. Edwards, D. Lito
  - Sportscenter - Lead, 1991 October (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0686)
  - FuquaVision Ep #1, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0699)
    Program Length: 18mins
  - FuquaVision Ep #2, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0700)
    Program Length: 17mins20secs; Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-011
  - FuquaVision Ep #3, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0701)
    Program Length: 22mins; Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-031
  - The Best of FuquaVision, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0702)
    Program Length: 31mins 15secs; Cable13 tape number: 8908-60-716
  - Talk to Me #4, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0703)
    Program Length: 47mins; Other notes: Peeler, Random Guests
  - Shock-Value Promo, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0704)
    Other notes: Public Enemy "Shut 'em Down" Poorboys - Interview
  - 3rd Eye Video 1, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0705)
    Cable13 tape number: 9009-60-024; Other notes: Crew: McIntyre, Public Enemy, 3rd Bass, Pylon, Lavalove, Spaceman, Spliff, Flyin' Mice, Radio Waves, Museum Exhibit
  - 3rd Eye Video 2, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0706)
    Program Length: 53mins36secs
  - 3rd Eye Video 3, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0707)
    Other notes: Intro, Grinning Evil Death
  - Freewater Films "The Godmother", 1991-1992 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0708)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-123; Other notes: By Andy Hagler, (copy of film transfer master: 9/24/87) (transferred from 16mm 8/18/87)
  - "Monday", 1991-1992 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0709)
    Program Length: 20mins; Other notes: by Donna Lennard
  - Freewater Films "Oblivion", 1991-1992 (Box 59, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0710)
    Cable13 tape number: 8811-60-605; Other notes: C13 copy
  - Cameron Corner Opening, 1991-1992 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0711)
  - Cameron Corner Opening, 1991-1992 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0712)
  - Freewater Films, 1991-1992 (Box 60, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0713)
    Program Length: 57mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2
  - In My Room, 1991-1992 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0714)
    Program Length: 53mins17secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep #4; Other notes: Guests: Seth Krauss, Dancing Devils
  - In My Room, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0715)
    Program Length: 55mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #6; Other notes: Guests: Scarlett, Uncle Harry
  - Freewater Films "Oblivion" & "Easy Answers", 1991-1992 (Box 72, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0716)
  - 1991 Duke Yearlook (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0009)
    Other notes: Crew: John Mark Reidy, Brent Christensen, Danny McCrary, Fran Mason
  - Kammerer Submissions, 1991 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0010)
    Other notes: "From Blood to Wine" M. David Messinger, "All About Eve" Laura Lee Tawney, "Trephining" Michael McIntyre, "Aesthetic Standard" John Angelo, "Perceptions of Tranquility" Michael Goldstein, "Super Dude!" Steve Reissner, "Taken In" Max Day, "The Role" Adam Joyce, "I am on Top of Me" Elizabeth Asch, "Man on the '90s IV: Fatherhood" Tom Oetting
  - Cameron Corner #2, 1991 January 15 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0663)
    Other notes: Maryland, Tech, Wake
  - Basketball: Duke vs UNC, 1991 January 19 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0664)
    Cable13 tape number: 8807-20-341
  - Duke SportsCenter, 1991 January 20 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0665)
    Cable13 tape number: Ep #2; Other notes: UNC hoops - men/women, Midseason NBA, Host: Dan Bernstein, Crew: Steve Goldberg, Casey Zimmer
  - Cameron Corner #3, 1991 January 21 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0666)
    Program Length: 27mins30secs; Other notes: UNC Game
  - Cameron Corner, 1991 January 22 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0002)
    Program Length: 29mins10secs; Cable13 tape number: #5; Other notes: Highlights: Delaware, Northeastern, Georgia Tech, Wake Forest, Virginia, NC State, FSU, Newton Rundown, Host: Steven Ross
  - Cameron Corner #4, 1991 January 28 (Box 55, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0667)
    Other notes: Christian Laettner, NC State, Clemson
  - Chuck D. and H. Allan Studio-Shoot, 1991 January 29 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0668)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2)
  - Chuck D. and H. Allan Studio-Shoot, 1991 January 29 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0669)
    Program Length: 54mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2)
  - Harry Allen & Chuck D in Cable 13 Studios, 1991 January (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0040)
  - Duke SportsCenter #3, 1991 February 03 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0656)
    Program Length: 22mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: 9009-30-041; Other notes: Duke vs Notre Dame, Duke vs Georgia Tech, ACC highlights, Christian Ast interview, Duke preview (VA, MD, LSU)
  - Cameron Corner #5, 1991 February 04 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0657)
    Program Length: 31mins; Other notes: Greg Koubeck, Ga. Tech, ND
  - Basketball: Duke vs UVA, 1991 February 07 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0658)
  - Cameron Corner #6, 1991 February 11 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0659)